八卦天后在此
gossip girl here--your once
你能接触曼哈顿上层糜烂的生活的
And only source into the scandalous lives of
唯一途径
Manhattan'slite.
在塔斯堪等你的那些天有点点难堪
Waiting for you in Tuscany the first few days were mildly humiliating.
但当我知道你不会出现以后  我就释然了
But when I realized you weren't gonna show, I rallied.
幸运的是  我这趟旅行结识了一个朋友
Luckily, I made a friend on the trip over.
其实我叫马库斯・比顿
My name is actually Marcus Beaton.
我是英国人还是个勋爵
I'm british and a lord.
拜托你不要和他走
Please don't leave with him.
你是想说整个暑假你都没有找乐子吗
You're telling me you didn't have any fun with anyone all summer?
我觉得我还没准备好  有时我还是会想着丹...
I don't think I'm ready. i-i still miss Dan sometimes.
我一直迫使自己转移注意力
Well, I've just been trying to distract myself the best I can.
本以为再见到你我会觉得到我们当初分开是对的
I was hoping when I saw you, I would know that we did the right thing.
但是我没有这种感觉  一点也没有
But i-i don't feel that way. I don't feel that way at all.
-那如何解释你和内特的种种传闻呢?  -纯属虚构
What about all those rumors I heard about you and Nate? completely untrue.
只是用这个来堵我失恋的闲言
They just got people off my back about being sad,
内特又能做喜欢的事
And then Nate could do whatever he wanted.
你告诉我你的地下女友比你大
When you told me your secret girlfriend was older,
还以为指的是学校
I thought you meant college.
更别提凯瑟琳已经结婚了
Not to mention, Catherine's married.
我只希望她能尝尝我的痛苦
I just wish I could make her feel as badly as I feel right now.
这个好办
You totally can.
我真不敢相信  你竟公然在
I can't believe that you would try to make me jealous
-我老公和朋友们面前这样刺激我  -奏效了么
In front of my husband and our friends. well, did it work?
效果明显
Completely.
我一个暑假都不能把你忘了
I haven't been able to get you out of my head all summer.
夏天就要结束的时候
As summer comes to an end,
我很愿意跟大家分享我的趣事
I'd like to share a few of the things I've learned about fun in the sun.
八卦天后向导
"gossip girl's guide to summer,
夏季特刊一号--工作时千万别睡着
" tip number one-- don't fall asleep on the job.
转播最好的就是清晨口气和尴尬的对话
The best hookups are free of morning breath and awkward conversation.
唯一一件比化妆更费劲的事情就是起床
The only thing harder than making up is waking up.
早安
Morning.
怎么了
What?
我很抱歉  我有点...
I'm sorry. i-i'm just a little, um...
不知所措吗
Overwhelmed?
有点混乱
Confused.
昨晚...
Last night was...
太棒了
It was amazing.
也有点混乱
And confusing.
我也有点混乱
Okay. now I'm-- I'm a little confused.
昨晚你的表现让我觉得十分浪漫
Well, it was so romantic what you did, showing up here,
而且让我觉得我们在一起没错
And it feels so right to be together.
但是你开始后悔了
But you're having second thoughts.
没有  我就是觉得我们应该...
No. i-i just think that we should think...
在我们和好之前先想想  对吗
Before we get back together, right?
没错  我觉得  这就已经意味着我们和好了
Y-yeah, I mean, I thought-- I thought this meant we were back together.
对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
没关系
No, you're not.
还是很抱歉
No, I'm not at all.
我们都不要说抱歉  我想保持现状
And neither am i, and--and I want to keep it that way.
这是个大决定  而且我们因为一件事分手过
But this is a big decision, and--and we did break up for a reason...
很多事情
Many reasons.
但是这都不是我们的错
But this was never our problem.
回城以后我们再见
I will see you back in the city...
穿戴整齐
Mmm. fully clothed...
周围有很多人  好吗
With lots of people around. okay?
我们还要谈一谈
We'll talk.
对  谈谈你的问题
Yeah, about our problems.
听起来不错
That sounds great.
夏季特刊二号--夏天里没有"我们"  只有"你"和"我"
Summer tip number two-- there's no "we" in summer, only "u" and "me."
先搞清楚你的身份地位
Find out where you stand before you find yourself stood up.
所有人都可以在七八月时热吻  但九月就不可以吗
Anyone can canoodle in july and august, but will he be gone by september?
接下来是什么
So what's next?
我正想我早餐吃什么  来点法式土司和咖啡
I was thinking breakfast-- a little french toast, some coffee.
不
No.
自从你不去普林斯顿或者乔治城大学
I mean, since you don't go to Princeton or Georgetown,
我猜想你会不会返回学校
I assume you're not headed back to college.
你现在想回哪里  还是待在这里
So where are you headed? are you staying here?
如果我说你去哪我就去哪会不会太鲁莽
Would it be too forward of me to say I'll go wherever you go?
我真的很荣幸  绅士
I'd be honored, milord.
布莱尔  你可没这么叫过我
Blair, you don't have to call me that.
-从来没有  -我知道  别担心
In fact, you shouldn't-- I know. don't worry.
我都通宵阅读《德布雷特氏贵族名鉴》
I was up all night reading "Debrett's Peerage."
我现在精通贵族规矩  我都准备好去见女王
I'm well versed in your lordly ways, and I'm ready to meet the queen,
顺便告诉你  我是从DVD上面看来的
Which I also watched on dvd, b.t.w.
看来你已经准备的相当充分了
Well, I can see that you are quite prepared.
那当然了  我要回城去了
As you've probably guessed, I have to get back to the city.
大四正在等着我
Senior year awaits.
我想想
Mm. let me think.
一个美丽的女孩  生活在纽约的秋季
A beautiful girl, autumn in new york.
-我觉得我应该想办法自娱自乐  -真的吗
Well, I think I could find some way to entertain myself. really?
当然  我家人很愿意我在一个地方待一段时间
Absolutely. my family will be glad I'm staying in one place for a while.
你的家人啊  我好想见见公爵和公爵夫人
Oh, your family. I'd love to meet the duke and duchess.
公爵夫人  嗯  会见到的
Duchess. right. w-well, we'll see.
请原谅  失陪一下
Will you euse me for a moment?
马库斯勋爵有点不对头
Things are going south with lord Marcus.
谁是马库斯勋爵  詹姆斯?
Who's lord Marcus? James.
事实证明他只是假装自己是个平民
It turns out that he was only pretending to be a commoner.
就像罗马假日那样
It's like "roman holiday,"
只是我成了格利高里・派克  而他是奥黛丽・赫本
Only I'm Gregory Peck, and he's Audrey Hepburn.
突然间事实都很明显了
Oh, suddenly it's all so clear.
他不是一个大学生
He's not really a college student.
他是个勋爵  我好爱他
He's a lord, and I love him.
我相信你说的  但是布莱尔  你爱他?
Okay, I'm gonna take your word for it, but, Blair, love?
喜欢  非常喜欢
Like, very much.
不仅因为汤姆・汉克斯在di夫人的葬礼上给他纸巾
And not just because Tom Hanks gave him a kleenex at lady di's funeral.
你真要我相信你不只是在报复恰克?
And you really expect me to believe this isn't all about revenge on Chuck?
报复已经是陈年旧事了
Revenge is so 12 hours ago,
只是马库斯恰好是最好拜斯替代者
And just because Marcus happens to be the perfect post-Bass
味觉清洗剂并不代表他自己不是道好菜
Palate cleanser doesn't mean he isn't a delicious dish in his own right.
听起来你俩还真是心心相印
Okay, so it sounds like you guys are soul mates.
-那问题出在哪  -他对未来摇摆不定
What exactly is the problem? he's being vague about the future.
-马库斯  -你好
Marcus. hey.
-恰克  -我正想吃点东西
Hello, Chuck. I was just getting something to eat.
-不介意我坐这吧  -其实我正和布莱尔一起吃饭呢
Do you mind if I join you? I do, yes. uh, I'm dining with Blair.
我觉得我该告诉你我知道你们交往过
And I feel I should tell you, I know you two have a history.
在这儿谁不是呢  不过现在是你和布莱尔
Around here, who doesn't? but you're with Blair now.
我懂了  没理由不礼貌一下的
I get that. there's no reason we can't be civil.
毕竟这是你们引以为豪的特点啊
After all, isn't that a trait your people pride themselves on?
没错
Right.
为了英格兰
Well, for England then.
我们能坐下吗
Shall we?
当然了
We shall.
等等  你刚发现这家伙的真正身份
Wait, you just found out this guy's real identity.
就开始忧心你的将来是不是太早了
I think it's a little soon to be worrying about the rest of your lives.
又不是仅仅这一年
But not the rest of the year.
会被嘲笑的  专业网球手和城里人  我是他羞于见人的秘密
It's the season for flings-- tennis pros and townies. I'm his secret summer shame.
布莱尔・霍道夫  被人嘲笑?
Blair waldorf--a fling?
你可不是什么低档货呀
Hmm. you're not exactly low maintenance.
说到这个  你昨晚在哪
Speaking of, where were you last night?
那个救生员也去那派对了
Did the lifeguard turn up at the party,
还是你找到另外的一次性用品了
Or did you find another disposable?
抱歉  布莱尔  我得挂了
Uh, sorry, Blair. I have to go.
瑟琳娜  等等
Wait. Serena!
-我还以为你会...  -我以为你上火车了
Hi. hey, I thought you were gonna... I thought you'take the train.
-上...上火车  是啊  -但你搭了小巴  我也是
Take the--the train. yeah. but you're taking the jitney. me, too.
我只是想用停工期的时间来
I-i was--i was just gonna use some of that downtime to do some of the
-想想我们说过的  -你本该如此  因为
Thinking that we talked about. and you should, you know, just 'cause,
我们不会弄明白的
Um, we're not gonna make out,
又不是说我们得不见彼此  是啊  我们又不是小动物
It doesn't mean we have to totally avoid each other. yeah, right. well, we're-- it's not like we're-- wee animals.
我想  我们能坐同一辆公车而且不会
I think--i think we can share the same bus without, uh,
一起逃掉
R-running off together.
-我要坐这  -那我坐这
I'm gonna sit over here. I'll be here.
这是我的
And that's me.
太好了  我会给你打电话的  请吧
Fantastic. I'll call you. please.
恰克  你干吗坐我的座位
And, uh... Chuck, what are you doing in my chair?
我们约好了去恰克爸爸的俱乐部打壁球
Oh, we've got a date to play squash at Chuck's father's club.
查尔斯  坐一边去
Charles, sidebar.
事实上  我们还没完呢
Actually, we weren't finished.
我的语调没上升吧  那不是问句
Notice how my voice didn't go up at the end? not a question.
壁球?  我会压扁你的
Squash? I'll squash you.
布莱尔  那只是个游戏
It's just a game, Blair.
对我来说不是 恰屁眼 我喜欢他
Not to me, bass-hole. I like him.
我也是  很明显  他没有多少朋友
And so do i, and apparently, he doesn't have too many friends.
恰克刚告诉我他和瑟琳娜马上就要走了
Chuck just informed me that he and Serena are leaving immediately.
我能搭你的车回城吗
Do you think I could catch a ride back into town with you?
当然了
Of course.
妈妈  这里看起来真漂亮
Hey, mom. it's looking really nice out here.
谢谢  我睡不着  所以早起了
Thanks. I couldn't sleep, so I got up early.
你要去哪吗
Are you going somewhere?
是啊  事实上我打算回城了
Yeah, I'm gonna head back into the city, actually.
但假日还没结束呢  是啊  我知道
But there's still a few more days of vacation. yeah, I know.
我想在开学前回去安顿好会好点
I figured it'd be good to get back in and settled before school starts.
我是说路易莎在家里呢  对吧
I mean, Louisa's at the house, right?
这不是什么大事  是啊
It's--it's not a big deal. no.
我还不想告诉你
I haven't wanted to tell you this,
不过你很快会知道的
But you're going to find out soon enough.
知道什么
Find out what?
联邦检察官已经认为
The federal prosecutor has taken your
你爸爸出城是承认了他的罪行
Father's leaving town as an admission of guilt.
他们要没收我们的资产
They want to forfeit our assets...
当作赔偿
For restitution.
什么  他们要没收我们的钱财?
What, they wanna take our money?
还没呢  不过他们冻结了我们的帐户
Well, not yet, but they have frozen our accounts.
现在他们正在给我们的资产编录
And now they're making an inventory of everything that we own.
-我向你爷爷求助  -什么  你和爷爷说了?
I asked your granddad for help. what, you told grandpa?
这没什么好处
Not that it did any good.
你能想像到
As you can imagine,
他很不高兴我让你爸爸离开
He's not very happy with my role in your father's departure.
至少从那时起  我们间的联系就断了
For the time being at least, I've been cut off.
真不敢相信你都知道  却不告诉我
I can't believe you knew all this, and you didn't say anything.
整个夏天  我还希望我能处理呢  也许我还能
All summer, I kept hoping I could make it go away, and maybe I still can,
-这就是为什么我要你缄默  相信你妈妈能处理好
Which is why I need you to keep your chin up and trust that your mother's got this handled.
-不  他走时  爸爸要我照顾好你的  你是这么做了
No, when he left, dad told me to take care of you. and you are.
内特  我们别再争论这个了  求你了
Nate, let's not fight about this, please.
建议三  不要再匆忙中赏花
Tip number three-- take time to smell the flowers.
妈妈  我要走了  这件事我们以后谈  好吗
Mom, I gotta go. let's talk about this later, okay?
美梦总会有醒的那一天
It's true that all good things must come to an end,
当然  八月也不例外
And august is no exception.
人们悲秋不是没有原因的
They don't call it "fall" for nothing.
我是内特  有事请留言
Hey, this is Nate. please leave a message.
内特  我是凯瑟琳
Nate, it's Catherine.
听好  我想说昨晚的行为可不明智
Listen, last night was not smart.
不  是非常非常愚蠢的行为
In fact, it was very, very stupid,
所以  为什么下次我们不聪明点
Which is why we're gonna have to be much more clever
期待以后再城里日子  收到留言请回电
When we get back to the city. call me when you get this.
亲爱的
Oh. darling.
公爵夫人  我收拾东西走的时候你不在家
Duchess, you weren't home when I packed up.
我只是想在我走之前跟你和爸爸说再见
Just wanted to say good-bye to you and dad before I left.
你父亲去波士顿了  明天才回来
Well, your father's run up to boston till tomorrow,
但我保证他随时都想着你
But I'm sure he sends his love.
这样吧  今天我们在城里吃晚饭
Listen, I'll see you in the city for dinner.
-我想听听你的夏天趣闻  -还有我爱你
I want to hear all about your summer. and me, yours.
到时候见
See you then.
曼哈顿  我们来了
Ah. manhattan, here we come.
布莱尔  为此欢呼吧
Cheers to that, Blair.
还有什么比满是气泡的香槟更好的欢迎方式吗
Nothing says "welcome home" like a bottle of bubbly...
你准备好了吗?
Ready?
当然也有绯闻的泡泡
Aah! and a scandal bubbling.
打扰了  我的杂志我看完了
Sorry. um, I'm done reading my magazine...
还有我知道你喜欢...
Oh. and I know that you like...
乐评  所以如果你想看的话 你可以拿去
The music reviews, so if you want to read it, you can.
谢谢
Thank you.
来一个吗
Want one?
不用了  谢谢  我不想吃
Oh, no thanks. I'm good.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
没事儿
It's okay.
那么  接下来你是有什么计划
So? what are your plans later?
我的意思是  除了去和你的新朋友恰克玩壁球
I mean, besides racquet sports with your new friend Chuck?
公爵夫人希望我们去吃晚餐
Oh, the duchess was hoping we'd get dinner.
晚餐  我非常想和你母亲一起吃饭
Dinner? I'd love to have dinner with your mother.
她是我继母  准确的说
Oh, she's my stepmother, actually,
要不是因为这一点  她对我来说一点也不重要
Not that this makes her an any less forceful presence in my life.
但是我意思是我们一起吃晚饭  她和我
But I meant we are having dinner--she and i.
我们整个夏天都没有见面了  所以...
We haven't seen each other much all summer, so...
当然  我理解
Oh. of course. I understand.
只是
It's just...
你会错过我的大派对
You'll be missing my big party.
你要办个派对
You're having a party?
我都不敢相信我没跟你提起过
I can't believe I didn't mention it.
每一年我都会为朋友们举行一个派对
Every year I have a big "welcome back
主题就是  欢迎回到纽约
To the city" party for all my friends.
这是全年我最期待的事情
It's only my favorite event of the year.
那我告诉公爵夫人换个时间再聚
Then I'll tell the duchess we'll catch up another time.
没有必要这么做  但是谢谢你
You don't have to, but thank you.
并无冒犯之意  但是你不觉得你有点过分了?
No offense, but don't you think you're a little outmatched?
玩壁球吗
At squash?
8年级的时候我就开始和我父亲一起打了
I've been playing my father since the eighth grade.
-马库斯能玩的多好  -没有我的意思是  作为个男人
How good can Marcus be? no, I mean, as a guy.
布莱尔想做公主
Blair wants to be a princess,
你目前最大的成就就是有burlesque club的股份
And your greatest achievement is owning part of a burlesque club.
这就是我为什么不得不去了解他
Which is why I have to get to know him.
你看  没有人是完美的
See, no one's that perfect.
一旦我发现了他的破绽  我就会设法追布莱尔
Once I get him out of the way, then I'll have a clear shot at Blair.
当你像个刺客般说话时  这就是爱
Oh, you know it's love when you start talking like an assassin.
我想你是妒忌我的新好友了
I think you're jealous of my new best friend.
我一直希望出现个人来代替我一会儿了
Well, I have been hoping someone would tag in for a while now.
喂
Hello?
现在不方便说
Uh, I can't talk right now.
我到家给你电话
I'll have to call you when I'm home.
如果你要为你帮什么私事
Hey, if you need to work out the details of your takedown,
-只管告诉我  -你真了解我  但是没问题
Don't let me stop you. you know me well, but it's nothing.
虽然还有点乱  但是我觉得应该对你胃口
It's still kind of a mess, but I think you get the idea.
怎么样
Well?
你什么都没有说
You're being very quiet.
是表示赞美呢还是批评
Is that good quiet or bad quiet?
拜托  我很怕
Come on. I'm freaking out.
我才怕
I'm freaking out.
这个地方真是太棒了  肯定会有客人来的
This place is amazing. people might actually come here.
这就是我想的
That was the idea.
我知道  但是当我说要把储藏室改成咖啡屋
I know, but when I talked about converting our storage space into a cafe,
我想到的只有折叠桌和咖啡机
I was thinking of a folding table and a coffeemaker.
瓦内萨  谢谢你  你用这大礼来欢迎我回家
Vanessa, thank you. this is a great homecoming present.
这正是我想要的
It's exactly what I needed.
什么你还想要什么  回家不好吗
What you needed for what? aren't you happy to be home?
不  当然好
Yeah, of course.
我等不及孩子们从汉普顿回来
I can't wait till the kids get back from the hamptons.
我想他们都想疯了
I miss 'em like crazy.
当然他们也很想你  但是...
And they miss you, too, but...
没有但是  我的夏天非常棒
No buts. I had a great time this summer.
我都快忘了那种人在旅途的感觉了
I had forgotten what it was like to be on the road,
那种一夜又一夜的演唱会
Performing for a live audience night after night.
现在你都想起来了
And now that you remember...
我非常珍惜这些记忆
I'm grateful for the memory.
话说回来这里是不是供应咖啡之类的呢
Now does this place actually serve coffee or what?
当然  有咖啡
Yes, it does.
速度点  谢谢
Uh, to go, please.
我要去市区
I need to head downtown.
家常咖啡  我请
One house blend, on the house.
-看看楼上能找到什么  -劳驾
And see what else you can find upstairs then. excuse me.
-你是内特 阿齐布尔德  -是我
You Nate Archibald? yeah.
这儿是我家  该我提问吧
Since this is my house, how about I ask the questions?
没事  你的家庭律师正在楼上监督
Don't worry. your family's lawyer is upstairs, supervising.
监督什么  具体说?
Supervising what, exactly?
我们
Us.
我们已进入你的家
We've moved into your house,
对你全家所拥有的一切物品进行调查
And we're going through every single thing your family owns.
看来你真的乐在其中啊  是不是
Wow. you're actually enjoying this, aren't you?
听着  没人想来搞庭院贩售会
Look, no one wants to hold a yard sale.
我们只想把你父亲关起来
We want your father locked up.
我们早就告诉起诉方  我们不知道他在哪
No, we already told the prosecutors we don't know where he is.
那太糟了
That's too bad.
-我们会处理  -也许你是会
We'll deal with it. maybe you will.
但在仔细搜查了你妈妈的衣柜之后
But after spending so much time in your mom's closet,
我想我了解这位夫人了
I feel like I know the lady.
我想她的心态不会调整的那么好
I don't think she'll adjust so well.
你好  我是凯瑟琳  请留言
Hi. it's Catherine. leave a message.
是我  听着  我非常需要找人谈谈
Hey. it's me. uh, listen, I really need to talk to someone.
所以  我想跟你谈谈
So, um, I need to talk to you.
所以如果你可以  请打给我
So if you can call me, please.
看起来你玩得不在状态啊
Something tells me you're off your game.
有什么我能帮忙的
Anything I can help with?
没人能帮忙
Uh, no one can help.
你肯定?
You sure?
是公爵夫人  就那回事
Well, it's the duchess. you know how it is.
跟我说
Tell me.
没人真正能达到完美
No one's ever good enough.
我约会过许多一流的女孩  她总能请她们走人
I've dated a lot of topflight girls, and she always sends them running.
就好象  她能看透她们的内心
It's like--and she gets inside their heads,
-找到她们最大的恐惧  然后  -无情地让她们暴露出来
Figures out their worst fears and just--- ruthlessly exploits that fear.
确实粗暴
It's rough.
更别说她完全控制了我父亲意志
Not to mention, she's completely got my father's ear.
当然  布莱尔非常想见她
Of course, Blair is desperate to meet her.
只要布莱尔打定主意...
And when Blair sets her mind on something...
确实
Exactly.
你打得很棒
That's a match.
我很希望下次能再跟你玩  但我现在该准备去布莱尔的派对了
I'd say let's keep at it, but I have to get ready for Blair's party.
-派对  -对
Party? right.
谢谢你  恰克  我们下次再玩
Thanks, Chuck. we should do this again.
哈德森见
See you at the Hudson.
好极了
Perfect.
上次跟你换手机号有点问题
And, uh, there was a problem with your cell earlier.
-我怎么没有你家的号码  -好
Why don't I get your home number? yeah, sure.
现场报道  恰克・拜斯把他新的永远最好的朋友加入了快速拨号组
Spotted--Chuck Bass putting his new b.f.f. on speed dial.
这究竟是美好的男孩友谊的开始...
Is it the beginning of a beautiful bro-mance...
-这比赛很棒  -我最近都有空
That was a good match. you nearly had me.
还是布莱尔成为英国贵妇希望落空的先兆
Or the end of Blair's bid to be british?
干得好  多洛塔  这些我很满意
Well done, Dorota. I like what I'm seeing.
就把阅览室作为天台  毛茛类选大丽花
Now make the library the sky terrace, the ranunculus dahlias,
凯歌香槟和罗兰百悦香槟  我想我们的派对也就差不多了
The veuve clicquot laurent-pierre, and I think we have ourselves a party.
谢谢  布莱尔小姐
Thank you, miss Blair.
但是宾客名单  远远不够
This guest list, however, is a complete page one.
上面都是你的朋友
But those are your friends.
那就请陌生人来
Then invite strangers.
我得像皇冠上最大的宝石  别人则是小珠宝
I have to present myself as a crown jewel, surrounded by other smaller,
她们得稍微带点瑕疵  但至少也要是真货
Slightly flawed gems, but quality stones nonetheless.
再想办法找点成年人来
And try to round up a couple people who can vote
这样就不完全是个高中生派对了
So it doesn't feel like a total high school party.
在哈德森开派对  收到你的信息了
A party at the Hudson, huh? I got your message.
啥事让你想开派对了
Since when are you having a party?
就因为马库斯觉得我还不够资格
Since it became clear that Marcus does not
-见他的家人  -我的天
Think I'm worthy of meeting his family. oh, my god.
我手头还有好多事要办呢
Obviously I have some more work to do.
-B  你没必要这么做的  -不  有必要
B., you don't have to do this. yes, I do.
马库斯曾跟格雷斯王妃的后裔约会过
Marcus dated the descendant of princess grace.
他的配偶必须有能力举办皇室宴会
His consort needs to be able to host royal
有能力与政界要人洽谈共饮
Dinners and hobnob with oligarchs and dictators.
如果说你跟政界要人找不到共同话题
Well, if you can't find common ground with a dictator,
-也没别的人可以了  -丹喜欢英式足球  是不是
I don't know who can. Dan likes soccer, right?
或者说足球  马库斯这么说来着
Or "football," as Marcus calls it.
-请他来怪不怪?  -不  不会吧
You think it'd be too weird if he came? um, no, not necessarily.
很好
Good.
我会给他打电话
You'll call him?
等等  这是不是意味着你觉得丹还是有赎罪的能力
Wait, so does this mean you actually think Dan has a redeeming quality?
只要他还知道他的功夫到家  我想他是一流的
As long as he knows his arse from his arsenal, I think he's aces.
这也许是个好机会  我们可以在一起相互谈谈
Well, this could be a good opportunity for us to get together and talk.
知道吗  我一直在考虑我跟他的分手...
You know, I have been thinking about the breakup-- ugh!
有什么好想的
What is to think about?
你总算跟那个倒霉的丹分了手  过去的瑟琳娜重新回来了
You're finally free from downer Dan, and I have my old Serena back.
快来吧  还有好多事要做呢
So come on. there's lots of work to do.
内特
Nate.
听着  我能否  能否跟你谈一下
Hey. look, could i, uh, could I talk to you for a second?
-我现在正有事  -你有女孩在这啊?
I'm actually in the middle of something. oh. do you have a girl here?
那你跟布莱尔的这段怎么样
I mean, what about your devotion to Blair?
不是女孩  是正事
It's not a girl. it's business.
我正在清算我在维克多拉的股份
I'm, uh, liquidating my shares in Victrola.
等等  你要把俱乐部卖了?  但你很喜欢那地方
Wait, you're selling the club? but you love that place.
恰克  如果你想打动布莱尔...
Chuck, if you're trying to impress Blair...
-我是说  拜托  -听着  你那天在轿车里说得很对
I mean, come on. look, what you said in the limo was right.
如果我要跟那人竞争  我就要上升到他的高度
If I'm gonna compete with this guy, I have to rise to his level.
是的  但你不觉得这有点偏激吗
Yeah, but don't you think that's a little extreme?
也许吧  但是在这种情况下  只能这么做了
Maybe, but given the situation, it's the right thing to do.
而且  我必须回到从前
And, uh, I should probably get back to it.
越快越好  我才有资本在布莱尔面前炫耀
The sooner I get it done, the sooner I can brag about it to Blair.
好吧  回头见了
Okay. all right. i, um, I'll see ya.
事情怎么样了
Yeah. what's going on?
你现在干嘛呢
What are you up to right now?
还要很长时间吗
Is this gonna take much longer?
我告诉过阿齐布尔德夫人我们必须今晚搞定
I told Mrs. Archibald we could have it done by tonight.
-喂  是我  -喂  收到我的短信了吗
Hey. hey. it's me. hey, you. did you get my message?
是的
Yeah.
是的  先别说话  听我说
Yeah, and listen, before you say anything else,
我必须告诉你  今早在公车上的事
I just want to let you know that, uh, this morning, on the--on the bus...
没错  我们都没有坚持计划  对吧
Yeah, we didn't exactly stick to the plan, did we?
不不  那计划确实不怎么好
Well, uh, no. the plan was deeply flawed.
我们太高估自己的自制力了
I think we overestimated our powers of restraint...
至少我是这样
Or, uh, i-i-i did, at least.
我也如此  不过我却认清了一件事
Yeah, me, too, but then I realized something.
-我也是啊  -真的吗
Yeah, me, too. really?
是这样的
Yeah, well, uh...
如果我们真的想弄明白一些事的话
I-i think if we want to figure anything out for real, you know,
应该分别待一段时间
We--we--we do need to take some time... alone.
行啊
Sure.
但是布莱尔可不这么想
Yeah, um, but Blair's not gonna like that.
布莱尔?
Blair?
没错  我打电话就是要说这事
Yeah, it's actually why I called.
从你那里学习足球超级联赛的知识
Your knowledge of premier league
是她综合课程的一部分
Football is integral to one of her schemes.
-她想让你参加派对  -派对吗
She just wants you to come to a party. a party?
是的  我也去  真的很想见你
Yeah, well, I'll be there, and I really wanna see you.
好吧  我想明天我们该制定一个新计划了
Yeah. yeah, I guess we can start with the new plan tomorrow.
你知道吗
You know,
很明显  他们是设法恐吓我们  让我们把我爸供出来
They're obviously just trying to scare us to get us to rat out my dad.
你确实知道他在哪儿的  对吗
You do know where he is, right?
没错  但是
Yeah, but...
但我不能说
I couldn't.
即使他做了那些不该做的事
Even after everything he's done.
先别想了吧
Just had to put it out there.
如果最坏的情况发生的话
But if the worst-case scenario comes true,
我保证  我和姐姐会教给你妈妈
I promise my sister and I will give your mom
一些事半功倍的方法的
Some good pointers on how to do more with less.
我倒真想看看呢
I'd love to see that.
救世军在这周六有一场大的义卖
The salvation army's having a bag sale on saturday,
鲁比知道村里有个买一送一的墨西哥餐馆
And Ruby knows this place in the village that has two-for-one taco night.
别说了
Stop it.
是一些墨西哥的女同志们  她们的乐队有时在那儿演出
It's lesbian-mexican. sometimes their band plays there.
稍等  好吗
Um, just one second, okay?
喂  妈妈
Hey, mom.
喂  内特
Hey, Nate.
我今天说的吓到你了  不好意思啊
I just wanted to apologize for scaring you this morning.
看来我能把这件事处理好了
It turns out I was able to fix things after all.
怎么处理  你没告诉他们爸爸在哪儿  对吧
How? you didn't tell them where dad is, did you?
当然没有
Of course not.
我向一个我们家的朋友那儿借了点钱
I just got a loan from a family friend.
-向谁借的  -这不重要
From who? that doesn't matter.
但我可不想听到你说  你把我们快破产的事
But I just find it hard to believe that you opened up to one
告诉了你读书俱乐部的那些女士
Of the book club ladies and told them we're completely broke.
他不是读书俱乐部的  是圈外人士
He's not in book club. he's outside of my regular circle.
-那你向一个刚认识的人借钱  -不是我向他借的
Oh, so you just asked someone you barely know for money? I didn't ask.
他主动提出的  我开始拒绝了
He offered, and when I tried to refuse,
-可是他坚持说这是他该做的  -他该做的?
He insisted that it was the right thing to do. the right thing to do?
你说他不是你的那个圈子里的人
You said he's outside of your regular circle?
难道是我认识他
Is he in mine?
内特  别管那么多了  做该做的事吧
Nate, please stop it. let me do this.
好吧  我不会再有意见了
Okay, fine. I won't bring it up again.
还好吗
Everything okay?
不怎么好  我得走了
No, actually, it's not. look, I gotta go.
我今晚回来  但我得先去找恰克
I'll come back later tonight, but I have to find Chuck first.
忘了说了  这地方真的棒极了
Oh, I forgot to tell you, the place looks great.
很高兴给你打了电话
I'm so glad I called you.
这个暑假我真的很想你
I really missed you this summer.
谢谢你
Thanks.
我也想你
Me, too.
是查尔斯・拜斯吗
Charles bass?
真抱歉
I'm sorry.
没想到您是如此年轻  并且如此美丽
I wasn't expecting anyone so young or so beautiful.
马库斯虽然不是我亲生
Just because I didn't give birth to Marcus
但并不代表我不关心他的幸福
Doesn't mean I'm any less interested in his well-being.
我不习惯跟小孩子们见面的  查尔斯
I don't usually take meetings with children, Charles,
你有什么要说的吗
So what do you have to say for yourself?
一言难尽
Plenty.
我的乖乖  看谁40岁了  或者至少是个保养了很好的38岁女人
Lordy, lordy, look who's 40-- or at least a well-preserved 38.
众所周知  恰克跟年长的女人有不解之缘
We knew Chuck had a thing for older women,
那么这次到底是风险交易还是严格意义上的生意?
But is this risky business or strictly business?
这真是太棒了
Wasn't that wonderful?
谢谢你们  英格丽德和碧儿翠思
Thank you, Ingrid and Beatrice.
我是英格丽德  她才是碧儿翠思
I'm Ingrid. she's Beatrice.
我是这个意思
That's what I said.
我太喜欢莫扎特了
Ah! I just love mozart.
那不是莫扎特的曲子
Uh, that wasn't mozart.
来  来
Come, come.
布莱尔  这些人是谁
Blair, who are these people?
多洛塔邀请了他们
Dorota invited them.
丹  不好意思
Uh, no-- Dan, hi! I'm sorry.
-来给你介绍下勋爵  -好的
Come meet the lord. okay.
你好  勋爵  我是丹・汉弗瑞
Uh, h-hello, lord. I'm Dan Humphrey.
马库斯・比顿  很高兴认识你  丹
Marcus beaton. nice to meet you, Dan.
你认识瑟琳娜吗
Do--do you know Serena?
认识
I do.
他认识
He does.
丹是个超级球迷
Dan is a football fanatic.
他是切尔西的超级球迷
He's a huge Chelsea fan.
我也是  我只喜欢巴黎世家商店
Oh, me, too. I just love the Balenciaga store.
喝完了吗
Freshen your drink?
是的  请
Mm. yes, please.
所以...
So, uh...
事实上她刚提到他是"勋爵"
Sh-she actually refers to him as "the lord"?
很高兴你能来
I'm so glad you're here.
恰克
Chuck.
我是丹
The name's Dan.
不是  恰克来了  但布莱尔并没邀请他
No, Chuck's here, and Blair didn't invite him.
可能是她后面加的
Maybe he's her plus-one.
-你来这儿干什么  -布莱尔
What are you doing here? Blair.
那是内特的...
That's Nate's...
我妈妈的朋友
Mom's friend.
我得离开一下  马上回来
Um, I have to go. I'll be back.
我想你可能想认识下我的朋友
I thought you might like to meet my friend.
为什么  那么她就能警告我打肉毒杆菌的效果
Why? so she can warn me about the effects of too much tox?
布莱尔  是吗
Blair, is it?
我是比顿公爵夫人
I'm duchess Beaton.
公爵夫人?
The duchess?
很高兴认识你
Nice to meet you.
花已经摆好了  不是吗
A little soon for flowers, no?
差一点点就摆好了
Just a few finishing touches.
我从没做过什么
A much better job than I could've ever done.
你只是不在这里罢了
You just weren't here to do it.
当然  但你在
Sure, but you were.
你干嘛不继续呢
How would you like to continue?
为什么  你一整天去哪了
Why? where have you been all day?
我去跟谭雅・多尼利见面了
I, uh, had a meeting with Tanya Donelly.
她正在办大学巡回演出
She has a college tour coming up.
又一个巡回演出?
Another tour?
丹跟珍妮怎么想
What do Dan and Jenny think?
在问他们之前  我想知道有没有可能性
Well, before I ask them, I wanted to see if it was even possible.
艾莉森的空档目前还没有人填补
Alison's open to coming back for a while longer,
但我知道暑假要结束了  你还要上课
But I know that summer's over, and you've got your schoolwork.
是的  学校的事让我没法分身
Yeah, homeschooling really ties me up.
如果  然而...
If, however,
如果你要求在你离开期间我不介意先留下
You're asking if I don't mind sticking around while you're away,
这不是在给你洗脑
It's not exactly brain surgery.
但你真的想要马上启程
But are you really sure you wanna leave so soon?
如果坦白讲  我不大确定我想干什么
Well, if I'm honest, I'm not sure what I want.
这次机会本应该是我新的起点
This was supposed to be my chance to get it all out of my system.
但我不知道我有多么的渴望
But I didn't know how much I missed it.
我还没结束
I'm not done.
太坦白了
Wow. that is honest.
不管你什么决定  我都乐意帮忙
Well, whatever you decide, I loved fixing up the place,
很高兴能够留下来
And I'd be happy to stick around.
有事就叫我
Just let me know.
谢谢
Thanks.
来吧  如果你真的喜欢他  就去道歉
Come on. if you really like him, just apologize.
我刚才干什么好事了
What good will it do me now?
公爵夫人?
Duchess?
很抱歉我刚才说的有关肉毒杆菌的话
I am so sorry about what I said about the botox.
你看起来很美
Your work is flawless.
我知道你跟恰克一起来的
Look, I know you're here with Chuck,
我能想象他是怎么形容我的  豪华轿车上的性爱
And I can only imagine what he's said about me-- limo sex,
折磨社交新人  讹诈
Social torture of freshmen, blackmail.
但我向你保证  我可以解释一切
But I assure you, there is an explanation for all of it.
省省吧  布莱尔
Save your breath, Blair.
恰克只字未提你的事
Chuck didn't tell me a thing.
他没有?
Oh. he didn't?
-等等  他  他没有?  -我让他别缠着我
Wait. he--he didn't? I told him not to bother.
对我来说并没有区别
None of it makes any difference to me,
因为没有什么能改变事实的  不管有多正面...
Because nothing will change the fact that despite your best efforts-- which are
完全显而易见的  顺便说下  马库斯绝不会跟卑微的霍道夫分手的
Completely transparent, by the way-- Marcus is never going to end up with a lowly Waldorf.
内特
Nate.
内特  凯瑟琳
Nate? Catherine?
你们两个认识?
You two know each other?
不  不  不  不  是的  暑假在读书俱乐部认识的
No. no, no, no. yeah, well, just from book club this summer.
仅此而已  他们没有其它的私下接触
But that's it. they've had no other personal contact.
布莱尔跟凯瑟琳的继子约会
Uh, Blair's dating Catherine's stepson.
凯瑟琳  内特是布莱尔的前男友
And, Catherine, Nate's Blair's ex.
怎么回事
What's this?
恰克的伴侣和布莱尔的伴侣是母子
Chuck's date and Blair's date are mother and son,
内特跟布莱尔是前情侣关系  内特跟妈妈在读书俱乐部
And Nate and Blair are exes, and Nate and the mother are in a book club?
现在是小说情节再现
Now there's a novel plot twist.
这个派对完全办砸了
This party's a complete bust.
我的人生也搞砸了
My whole life's a bust.
这是你应得的
Well, it serves you right.
你难道不是在计划说服马库斯你不是某个人么
You were scheming to convince Marcus you're someone you're not.
但我的初衷是好的
But my intentions were good.
我真的很喜欢他  我只是
I really do like him. I just...
只要我知道他喜欢我了
As soon as I knew he liked me,
我就会放手  不再管
I would have relaxed and dropped the manipulative
从此全身心投入做个最好的女朋友
Plotting and devoted myself to being the best girlfriend ever.
看见没?  谢谢你
See? thank you.
这才是我的b
There's my b.
把这女孩带给凯瑟琳看  她会同意你和马库斯在一起的
Show this girl to Catherine, and she'll want you to be with Marcus.
这才是你  做你自己
This is you. just be yourself.
是她提出的"霍道夫" 韵和"斯皮尔斯"
She made "Waldorf" rhyme with "Spears."
我可能已经开战了而且
I may as well have gone commando and
在尼拉的汉堡篮子里还开了派对
Held my party at Nyla's burger basket.
好吧
Fine.
当你站在这对自己愧疚并
While you stand here and feel sorry for yourself and
贬低肯特林的好人的时候  我要去找丹了
Denigrate the fine people of Kentwood, I'm gonna go find Dan.
开心点
Cheer up.
真不敢相信你居然这么对我
I can't believe you'd do this to me.
把公爵夫人带到布莱尔的派对来?  你担心什么呢?
Bring the Duchess to Blair's party? what do you care?
不  我知道钱的事
No, I know about the money.
内特...
Nate...
不  你不能为了给布莱尔留个好印象就试图卖了维克多拉
No. you weren't trying to sell Victrola to impress Blair.
你卖了向我家里放贷么?
You did it to loan my family money?
听着  你说得好像很坏似的.
Look, you say it like it's a bad thing.
不  也许你只是为了友好才这么做的
No, and maybe you were just doing it to be a friend,
但是我永远不会让你那么做  你知道的
But I would never let you do that, and you knew that,
-这就是为什么你不告诉我么  -是的  那又怎样?
Which is why you didn't tell me. yes, it is. so what?
怎样?  你暗里藏刀搞我妈妈?
So what? you go behind my back and make a deal with my mom?
她叫我来看看  我还以为你没事呢
She called me to see if I thought you were okay.
我都不知道她说的是什么
I didn't know what she was talking about,
因为你并没告诉我什么地方不对
Because you didn't tell me anything was wrong.
我告诉你哪不对--我最好的朋友当我的面撒谎
I'll tell you what's wrong-- my best friend lying to my face.
通常我会站在你这边
Look, normally, I would agree with you.
但是这种事你妈妈对我放得开了
But for your mom to open up to me about something like this,
-我会处理的  行了吧?  -怎么处理?
I'll handle it, okay? how?
丹  你要走么?
Dan, hey. you leaving?
是啊  我要去火车站接珍妮
Yeah, I have to get Jenny from the train.
我不知道你也回来了  跟你一起去呀?
I-i didn't know if you were coming back, so... how about coming with you?
我们离开这好么?
Why don't we get out of here?
我们跟谁开玩笑呢?
Who are we kidding?
你觉得我们是不是该忘记思想追随感受呢?
What do you say we just forget thinking and follow our hearts?
你确定你心里是这么想的么?  因为...
Are you sure that's your heart you're following? 'cause...
别说话  不然我会改主意的
Shut up, or I'll change my mind.
显然  世界上还有别的势力在这工作  那么...
Hey, clearly, there are other forces at work here in the universe, so...
势力比我们更强大
Mmm. forces much more powerful than us.
很高兴跟你聊天
I'm glad we had this little talk.
你们两个又和好了还是...
Oh, are you two back together or...
-不  这只是有一点友好的  -亲吻  是吧
Uh, uh, no. this was just a little, uh, friendly-- kiss, yeah. mm-hmm.
你要来么
Okay. are you coming?
图书馆见
In library, come meet me
不了  你们先走吧
Uh, no, no. you guys, uh, you guys should go ahead.
好吧
Oh. good.
这个电梯就要被使用了
'cause, uh, this elevator's gonna be in use.
真是一团糟
Hey. this is so messed up.
你前女友和我的继子在约会?  就是这样
Your ex dating my stepson? yes, it is.
我了解你  内特
But I actually do know you, Nate.
这不是困扰你的事
That isn't what's bothering you.
我想我正在着手解决
Well, I think I'm starting to get it, you know,
这个夏天结束了  事情怎么都变成现在这样
How things are gonna be now that the summer's over.
我是说
I mean,
有那么样个人确实不错
It would be kind of nice to have someone who could actually be there.
但这局面最好的可能就是
But when the best version of the situation
我会成为布莱尔的合法父亲
Is that I'm gonna become Blair's father-in-law?
-我想这需要时间来解决  凯瑟琳  -不  等等  内特
I think it's just time to move on, Catherine. no, wait, Nate.
好了  我现在就在这  我想跟你谈谈
Come on, I'm here now, and I want to talk.
告诉我发生什么了
Just tell me what's going on.
爸爸  是我
Hey, dad. it's me.
我跟丹谈过了  他正来火车站接我呢
Um, I talked to Dan, so he's gonna pick me up at the train station.
那么我就在家见你了  但是--哦  天呢!  停下!
So I'll just see you at home, but--oh, my god! stop it!
抱歉  爸爸  我们在打水仗  我要踢eric的屁股
Sorry, dad. I gotta go kick eric's ass in a water fight.
爱你  拜
Love you. bye.
谭雅 是我  鲁弗斯
Yeah. hey, Tanya. it's me--Rufus.
我想安妮・阿齐布尔德宁愿死也不愿失去她的房子和财产
I think Anne Archibald would rather die than lose her house, her things.
那是她全部的身份象征
They're her whole identity.
这就是为什么我不想让它发生
That's why I'm not gonna let that happen.
-我找到一个方法  -天  但是这不是她不想要一起生活的
I'll find a way. god, but it's not what she's gonna have to live without.
是她想要一起生活的
It's what she's gonna have to live with.
我是说  丑闻会毁了她的
I mean, a scandal will destroy her.
你能想象她看着她的房子被争夺
Can you imagine her watching her house seized,
她祖母的珠宝被拍卖么?
Her grandmother's jewels up for auction?
我跟你说过  我会解决这些问题的
I told you, I'll figure something out.
我能处理好  只是需要时间
I can handle this. I just need some time.
你能处理这些问题...
You can take care of this...
在我的帮助下
With my help.
这就是我们俩的事  没人会知道
It'd just be between you and me. no one would have to know.
我在乎你  内特  我会为你做的
I care about you, Nate. I would do it for you.
那我要为你做什么?
And what would I have to do for you?
多洛塔  你看过公爵夫人么?
Dorota, have you seen the Duchess?
在图书馆
In library.
我的上帝啊!
Oh, my effing god!
我没必要向你解释
Well, I don't have to explain myself to you.
没必要解释  我已经明白了
No explanation necessary. I think I got it.
凯瑟琳
Catherine?
如果你不介意  我想她和谈一会
She'll just be one more minute, if you don't mind.
给你
Here you go.
可以说下之前对于你的评判我有多抱歉吗
Can I just say how sorry I am that I judged you earlier?
你评判我
You judged me?
我以为你是个不谙世事的
I thought you were just a callow,
通过婚姻爬到上流社会的泳装模特
Social-climbing former swimsuit model who married above
缺乏安全感  自怨自艾
Her station only to be enslaved by her own insecurities.
但是看到你和我年轻的朋友在地板上翻云覆雨
But now that I've seen you rolling around on the floor with my
我知道你也是富有同情心的
Adolescent ex, I understand you have a compassionate side, too.
你想说什么  布莱尔
What are you saying, Blair?
我想你会发现对我心存同情
That I think you'll find it in your heart to take pity on me,
然后会以循序渐进的方式公平公正的
And in spite of my common, lowly, unroyal ways,
接受我和马库斯是真心相爱的事实
Accept that I have true feelings for Marcus and that he has them for me, too.
我想这对我们来说都好  你说呢
I think that would be the best thing for both of us, don't you?
-找到你了  -你好  亲爱的
Oh, there you are. hello, darling.
我来晚了吗
Am I too late?
听说你在布莱尔的派对上我就尽快赶来了  公爵夫人
As soon as I heard you were at Blair's party, duchess,
我知道我必须找到你进行损害管制
I knew I had to find you and do damage control.
是还在进行中  还是你已经把布莱尔吓的够呛了
Is there still time, or have you already scared Blair off?
不是这样的  布莱尔来这里是为了招待我
Not at all, dear. Blair here is a treat.
我明白为什么你对她这么一网情深了
I can see why you're so fond of her.
她从来都没喜欢过我的女朋友
She never likes my girlfriends.
她只是需要真正的了解我
She just had to get to know the real me.
你刚是说女朋友
Did you say girlfriend?
-她要求你帮她做衣服  -不可思议  对吧
She asked you to make her a dress? I know, right?
在火车上我已经画好一些素描了
I already did some sketches on the train.
-爸爸  -珍妮
Dad! Jenny! hey!
哦  想死我了  看到你真是太棒了
Oh! I missed you! it's so good to see you.
还有满满一厨房的食物  我快饿死了
Mmm. and a kitchen full of food. I'm starving. hey, dad.
-有卡普列塞沙拉  香蒜酱配汤团  -太好了
Yeah, a little caprese salad, a little gnocchi with pesto. yummy!
第一次汉弗瑞家的聚餐
First Humphrey family meal of the fall-- I
我想我们需要特别点的东西
Figured we should do something special. yeah.
我想知道关于汉普顿还有其它所有
I want to hear all about the Hamptons and everything else that
-这个夏天发生的事情  -看来珍妮有不少故事发生
Happened this summer. well, it sounds like Jenny's got some stories.
-丹也是  他告诉你他解决好了吗  -终于有结果了吗
So does Dan. did you hear he finished his? oh, it finally has an ending?
-暂时告一段落  -段落
Uh, well, this chapter does, yeah. chapter?
我还以为是个短剧呢
Yeah I thought it was a short story.
我在想把它写进小说
I'm thinking of reworking it into a novel.
小说  这可不是什么伟大的计划
Oh, a novel. that's not ambitious. yeah.
某些人觉得他的生活富有吸引力呀
Hmm. someone must think his life's pretty fascinating.
谢谢支持  同志们
Oh, thanks for the support, guys.
-会把你们两都写进去的  -你怎么样  爸爸
You're both being written out. well, what about you, dad?
你是美国最伟大的徒步旅行者之一
You were the one on the great american road trip.
是不是不虚此行呀
Any, uh, stories worthy of your memoir?
很有趣  但是金窝银窝比不上自己狗窝
Oh, you know, it was fun, but there's no place like home.
啊  真是个独到的想法
Aw! oh, that's an original thought.
如果你真的要写传记的话  你该想想找个代笔人
You know, if you do write a memoir, you should think about a ghostwriter.
我告诉过你你的背吃不消这种双层床的
You know, I told you that your back could never handle those bunk beds.
面对现实吧  你越来越老了
Mm. face it, dad. you're getting old.
-你们说的都对  -这个看上去很好吃
Yep. that's it all right. this looks good.
看上去棒极了
It looks fantastic.
你是对的  一如既往
You were right, as usual.
我不想说看我告诉过你的  但是...
Well, I don't want to say I told you so, but...
我只要做好自己  凯瑟琳喜欢我
All I had to do was just be myself, and Catherine loved me.
我为你自豪B
Oh, I'm proud of you, b.
太好了
Great.
瑟琳娜  可以回避一下吗
Actually, Serena, can we have a second?
我要把这个拿走
Um, I'll take that.
我这就走开  让你们独处
I'll just leave-- leave you two alone.
享受和公爵夫人 比顿的约会吗
Did you enjoy meeting Duchess Beaton?
是的
I did.
你的话里没有讽刺的味道  这有点  -志得意满
That's not sarcasm in your voice. it's-- victory. I know.
你想算计我但是适得其反
Your plan to ruin me totally backfired.
看来马库斯的妈妈远没有你变态
It turns out Marcus' mommy is even sicker than you are.
你进行的很不错
You got along great.
我想她已经有些认同我了
I think she recognized a part of herself in me.
或者说  我通过某人验证了她
Or rather, I recognized someone in her.
-我听不懂  -你只要知道你输了
I don't follow. all you need to know is that you lost.
但是可别太自责了
But don't be too hard on yourself.
-这只是无心之失  -明天又是新的开始
It was a solid effort. tomorrow's another day.
-晚安  恰克  -晚安  布莱尔
Good night, Chuck. good night, Blair.
嗨  内特
Hey, Nate.
看来和你预计的时间要长点
So that maybe took a little longer than you thought.
一点点  是的
A little bit, yeah.
听着
Uh, hey, listen.
很抱歉  但是我今天晚上回不来了
I'm--i'm so sorry, but I'm not gonna be able to make it back tonight.
我想到了  没关系  我也很累了
I-i figured. it--it's okay. I was tired anyway.
那我们再约吧
So we'll hang out another time.
当然  恩...
Oh, yeah, yeah, for sure. um...
那我待会打给你  好吗
So--so look, I'll call you later, okay?
好的  再见
Okay. bye.
再见
Bye.
我们还好吧
Are we good?
我们很好
We're good.
每个夏天
Every summer,
游客们至始至终都在寻找新的刺激和经验
Vacationers traverse the globe in search of new sights and experiences.
但当它变成丑闻的时候  我都会带把它回曼哈顿
But when it comes to scandal, I'll take manhattan every time.
欢迎回家  上东区的家伙们
Welcome home, upper east siders.
你知道你在想我
You know you missed me.
八卦天后
X.o.x.o., gossip girl.